[
  {
    "front": "괴물",
    "back": "Monster"
  },
  {
    "front": "실수",
    "back": "Mistake"
  },
  {
    "front": "휴가",
    "back": "Holiday"
  },
  {
    "front": "머무르다",
    "back": "Stay"
  },
 {
    "front": "배",
    "back": "Boat"
  },
 {
    "front": "항해하다",
    "back": "Sailing"
  },
 {
    "front": "낚시",
    "back": "fishing"
  },
  {
    "front": "오두막",
    "back": "Cottage"
  },
  {
    "front": "호수",
    "back": "Lake"
  },
  {
    "front": "장난/농담",
    "back": "Joke"
  },
  {
    "front": "만들다",
    "back": "Make"
  },
  {
    "front": "밧줄",
    "back": "Rope"
  },
  {
    "front": "당기다",
    "back": "Pull"
  },
  {
    "front": "놀란",
    "back": "Amazed"
  },
  {
    "front": "사진",
    "back": "Photograph"
  },
  {
    "front": "텔레비전",
    "back": "Television"
  },
  {
    "front": "신음하다/투덜거리다",
    "back": "Groaned"
  },
 {
    "front": "그림",
    "back": "Picture"
  },
 {
    "front": "읽다",
    "back": "Read"
  },
 {
    "front": "시간",
    "back": "Time"
  },
 {
    "front": "웃다",
    "back": "Laugh"
  },
 {
    "front": "기다리다",
    "back": "Wait"
  },
  {
    "front": "화난",
    "back": "Cross"
  }
]